{"items": [{"question": "miser", "answer": "penurious", "options": ["parsimony", "indigence", "penurious", "destitute"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "excessive economy", "answer": "parsimony", "options": ["parsimony", "destitute", "affluence", "indigence"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "poverty", "answer": "indigence", "options": ["indigence", "opulence", "destitute", "affluence"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "lacking food, clothing and shelter", "answer": "destitute", "options": ["affluence", "destitute", "opulence", "vicarious"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Abundant flow or supply", "answer": "affluence", "options": ["affluence", "opulence", "ephemeral", "vicarious"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "wealth", "answer": "opulence", "options": ["evanescence", "vicarious", "ephemeral", "opulence"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Experienced in place of another", "answer": "vicarious", "options": ["evanescence", "ephemeral", "euphemism", "vicarious"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Lasting a very short time", "answer": "ephemeral", "options": ["ephemeral", "euphony", "evanescence", "euphemism"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "disappear gradually", "answer": "evanescence", "options": ["euphemism", "evanescence", "eulogy", "euphony"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "An inoffensive or indirect expression that is substituted for one that is considered offensive or too harsh", "answer": "euphemism", "options": ["euphemism", "euphoria", "euphony", "eulogy"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "agreeable and pleasing sound", "answer": "euphony", "options": ["euphoria", "euthanasia", "eulogy", "euphony"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "A formal expression of praise for someone who has died recently", "answer": "eulogy", "options": ["badinage", "eulogy", "euthanasia", "euphoria"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "state of intence happiness and self-confidence", "answer": "euphoria", "options": ["badinage", "persiflage", "euphoria", "euthanasia"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "The act of killing someone painlessly", "answer": "euthanasia", "options": ["badinage", "euthanasia", "persiflage", "cliche"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "playful banter", "answer": "badinage", "options": ["bromide", "cliche", "badinage", "persiflage"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "good natured banter", "answer": "persiflage", "options": ["bromide", "persiflage", "cliche", "platitude"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "phrase that is overused", "answer": "cliche", "options": ["cliche", "platitude", "bromide", "anodyne"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Overfamilier statement", "answer": "bromide", "options": ["plateau", "anodyne", "platitude", "bromide"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "a flat remark despite the speaker's high hopes", "answer": "platitude", "options": ["plateau", "anodyne", "penurious", "platitude"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "capable of relieving pain", "answer": "anodyne", "options": ["anodyne", "parsimony", "penurious", "plateau"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "A relatively flat highland", "answer": "plateau", "options": ["parsimony", "plateau", "indigence", "penurious"], "answer_index": 2}], "title": "Word power Made Easy - Session 40.txt", "total": 21}